Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection
Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection
- Assorted Small Publishers
  - Publisher: Super Comics
    - Title from indicia: Danger, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Daring Adventures, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Doll Man, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Jungle Adventures, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Mystery Tales, Issues from: [1960s]
    - Title from indicia: Plastic Man, Issues from: [1960s]
    - Title from indicia: Spirit, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Strange Mysteries, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Torchy, Issues from: 1960s
  - Publisher: Tekno
    - Title from indicia: Isaac Asimov's I-Bots, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Neil Gaiman's Mr. Hero-The Newmatic Man, Issues from: 1990s
  - Publisher: Texas Comics
    - Title from indicia: Justice Machine Annual, Issues from: 1980s
  - Publisher: Timely
    - Title from indicia: Amazing Comics, Issues from: 1940s
      - Cover Title: Young Allies Featured in Amazing Comics
    - Title from indicia: Captain America Comics, Issues from: 1940s (Box 454)
  - Publisher: Toby
    - Title from indicia: Al Capp's Li'l Abner, Issues from: 1950s (Box 439)
    - Title from indicia: John Wayne Adventure Comics, Issues from: 1950s
  - Publisher: Tome Press
    - Title from indicia: Dinosaurs: An Illustrated Guide, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Jason and the Argonauts, Issues from: 1990s
  - Publisher: Topps
    - Title from indicia: Bombast, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Cadillacs and Dinosaurs, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Cadillacs and Dinosaurs
      - Cover Title: Cadillacs and Dinosaurs: The Wild Ones
    - Title from indicia: Captain Glory, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Dracula Versus Zorro, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Exosquad, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Jack Kirby's Secret City Saga, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Jack Kirby's Silver Star, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Jack Kirby's Teenagents, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: James Bond 007/Goldeneye, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Jurrasic Park, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Jurrasic Park Annual, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Jurrasic Park: Raptor, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Jurrasic Park: Raptors Attack, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Jurrasic Park: Raptors Hijack, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Lady Rawhide, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Lone Ranger and Tonto, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Lost World: Jurrasic Park, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Night Glider, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Ray Bradbury Comics, Issues from: 1990s (Box 440)
    - Title from indicia: Ray Bradbury Comics: Martian Chronicles, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Ray Bradbury Comics Special Edition, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Ray Bradbury's The Illustrated Man
    - Title from indicia: Ray Bradbury Comics: Trilogy of Terror, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Return to Jurrasic Park, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Satan's Six, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Satan's Six: Hellspawn, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Space: Above and Beyond, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Space: Above and Beyond--The Gauntlet, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Victory, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The X-Files, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Zorro, Issues from: 1990s
  - Publisher: Tower
    - Title from indicia: Dynamo, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Fight the Enemy, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Noman, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Thunder Agent Noman, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Thunder Agents, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Undersea Agent, Issues from: 1960s
  - Publisher: Treasure Chest
    - Title from indicia: Treasure Chest of Fun and Fact, Issues from: 1960s, 1970s
  - Publisher: T.S.R.
    - Title from indicia: Buck Rogers, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Warhawks, Issues from: 1990s
  - Publisher: United Features Syndicate
    - Title from indicia: Comics on Parade, Issues from: 1940s
      - Cover Title: Comics on Parade: Li'l Abner
    - Title from indicia: Sparkler Comics, Issues from: 1940s
  - Publisher: Upshot Graphics
    - Title from indicia: Flesh and Bones, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Miracle Squad, Issues from: 1980s
  - Publisher: Valiant (Box 441)
    - Title from indicia: Archer and Armstrong, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Armorines, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Bloodshot, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Bloodshot Yearbook, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Chaos Effect, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Deathmate, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Destroyer, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Eternal Warrior, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Eternal Warrior Yearbook, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Geomancer, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Harbinger, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Harbinger, Issues from: 1990s (Box 442)
    - Title from indicia: Harbinger Files, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The H.A.R.D. Corps, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Magnus Robot Fighter, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Magnus Robot Fighter/Nexus, Issues from: 1990s (Box 443)
    - Title from indicia: Magnus Robot Hunter, Solar, Man of the Atom and Turok, Issues from:1990s
      - Cover Title: Valiant Reader
    - Title from indicia: Magnus Robot Fighter Yearbook, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Ninjak, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Ninjak Yearbook, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Psi-Lords, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Rai, Issues From: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Rai and the Future Force, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Second Life of Doctor Mirage, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Secret Weapons, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Secrets of the Valiant Universe, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Shadowman, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Shadowman, Issues from: 1990s (Box 444)
    - Title from indicia: Shadowman Yearbook, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Solar, Man of the Atom, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Solar, Man of the Atom: Hell on Earth, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Timewalker, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Timewalker Yearbook, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Turok, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Turok, Child of Blood, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Turok, Dinosaur Hunter, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Turok, Dinosaur Hunter, Issues from: 1990s (Box 445)
    - Title from indicia: Turok, Dinosaur Hunter Yearbook, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Turok, The Empty Souls, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Turok, the Hunted, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Turok Redpath, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Turok, Spring Break in the Lost Land, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Turok, Tales of the Lost Land, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Turok, Timewalker: Seventh Sabbath, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Unity Yearbook, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Valiant Vision Starter Kit, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Visitor, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: The Visitor vs. The Valiant Universe, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-O Manowar, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-O Manowar/Iron Man: In Heavy Metal, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: X-O Manowar Yearbook, Issues from: 1990s
  - Publisher: Visual Editions (Box 446)
    - Title from indicia: Freckles, Issues from: 1940s
  - Publisher: Vital
    - Title from indicia: Plastic Man, Issues from: 1940s
  - Publisher: Vortex
    - Title from indicia: Mister X, Issues from: 1980s
  - Publisher: Wally Wood
    - Title from indicia: Heroes, Inc. Presents Cannon, Issues from: 1960s
  - Publisher: WaRP
    - Title from indicia: Blood of the Innocent, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: A Distant Soil, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Elfquest, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Elfquest: Blood of Ten Chiefs, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Elfquest: Hidden Years, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Elfquest: Jink, Issues from: 1990s (Box 447)
    - Title from indicia: Elfquest: Kings of the Broken Wheel, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Elfquest: Kings Cross, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Elfquest: Metamorphosis, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Elfquest: New Blood, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Elfquest: New Blood Summer Special, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Elfquest: The Rebels, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Elfquest: Siege at Blue Mountain, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Elfquest: Shards, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Elfquest: Wave Dancers, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Elfquest: Worldpool, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Myth Adventures, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Thunderbunny, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Unicorn Isle, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Warp Graphics Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Xanth Graphic Novel Vol. 1: Return to Centaur, Issues from: 1990s
  - Publisher: Western Publishing
    - Title from indicia: Bugs Bunny Comics-Go-Round, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney Christmas Parade, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Whitman
    - Title from indicia: Brothers of the Spear, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Buck Rogers, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Buck Rogers in the 25th Century, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Bugs Bunny, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Doctor Solar, Man of the Atom, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Flash Gordon, Issues from: 1980s (Box 448)
    - Title from indicia: Little Lulu, Issues from: 1970s, 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Little Stooges, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Pink Panther, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Popeye the Sailor, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Space Family Robinson, Lost in Space on Space Station One, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Starstream, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Tom and Jerry, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Turok, Son of Stone, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Bambi, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Cinderella, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Comics and Stories, Issues from: 1970s, 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Daisy and Donald, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Donald Duck, Issues from: 1970s, 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Huey, Dewey and Louie, Junior Woodchucks, Issues from:1970s, 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Jungle Book, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Mickey Mouse, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Peter Pan, Issues from: 1980s (Box 449)
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Uncle Scrooge, Issues from: 1970s, 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Walt Disney's Wonderful Adventures of Pinocchio, Issues from:1970s
    - Title from indicia: Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Wild Storm
    - Title from indicia: Gen 13, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Gen 13 Annual 1999, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Gen 13/Fantastic Four, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Gen 13: Going West, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Gen 13: Grunge Saves the World, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Gen 13: Medicine Song, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Gen 13: Wired, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Gen-Active, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek Special, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: All of Me, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: Divided We Fall, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: Enter the Wolves, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: Deep Space Nine--Embrace the Wolf, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: Deep Space Nine--N-Vector, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: The Next Generation--The Killing Shadows, Issues from:2000s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: The Next Generation--Perchance to Dream, Issues from:2000s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: Voyager--Avalon Rising, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: Voyager--Elite Force, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: Voyager--False Colors, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: Voyager--Planet Killer, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Superman/Gen 13, Issues from: 2000s
  - Publisher: Will Eisner
    - Title from indicia: The Spirit, Issues from: 1940s, 1950s
  - Publisher: Windjammer
    - Title from indicia: Bar Sinister, Issues from: 1990s
    - Title from indicia: Star Slayer, Issues from: 1990s
      - Cover Title: Star Slayer: The Director's Cut
  - Publisher: Wolf
    - Title from indicia: The Phantom, Issues from: 1990s
  - Publisher: Ziff-Davis
    - Title from indicia: Amazing Adventures, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Hans Christian Anderson, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Lars of Mars, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Perfect Love, Issues from: 1950s
- Underground Comics
  - Publisher: Aardvark-Vanaheim Inc. (Box 450)
    - Title from indicia: Neil the Horse Comics and Stories, Issues from: 1980s
  - Publisher: Almighty Publishing Company
    - Title from indicia: Funny Book, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Apex Novelties
    - Title from indicia: All New Zap Comix, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Black and white Comics, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Funny Animals, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Left-Field Funnies, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Mr. Natural, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Your Hytone Comix, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Zap Comix, Issues from: 1960s,1970s
  - Publisher: Big Apple Productions
    - Title from indicia: Big Apple Comix, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Boston Comicworks
    - Title from indicia: New Legends, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Bud Plant
    - Title from indicia: Anamoly, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: California Comics
    - Title from indicia: Barbarian Comics, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Cartoonists' Co-op Press
    - Title from indicia: Nard N' Pat, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Cocoanut Comix
    - Title from indicia: The "Dirty Duck" Book, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Morton of the Movement, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Company and Sons
    - Title from indicia: The Collected Cheech Wizard, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Dan O'Neill's Comics and Stories, Issues from: [1970s]
    - Title from indicia: Drool Magazine, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Psychotic Adventures Illustrated, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Tales of the Armorkins, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Glenn Bray and Basil Wolverton
    - Title from indicia: GJDRKZLXCBWQ Comics, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Golden Gate Publishing
    - Title from indicia: Artistic Comics, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The People's Comics, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Googiewaumer Comics
    - Title from indicia: Googiewaumer Comics, Issues from: 1960s
  - Publisher: Half-Ass Press
    - Title from indicia: Greaser Comics, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Hell Comics
    - Title from indicia: Air Pirates Funnies, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Air Pirates Funnies
      - Cover Title: Mickey Mouse Meets Air Pirates Funnies
    - Title from indicia: Noof Unnies, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Tooney Loons and Marijuana Melodies, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Joshua Quagmire (J.Q.) Enterprises
    - Title from indicia: Army Surplus Komikz Featuring Cutey Bunny, Issues from: 1980s
  - Publisher: Krupp Comic Works
    - Title from indicia: Bijou Funnies, Issues from: 1960s, 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Bizarre Sex, Issues from: 1970s, 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Death Rattle, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Deep 3D Comix, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Fever Dreams, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: High Adventure, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Home Grown Funnies, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Hungry Chuck Biscuits Comics and Stories, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Mom's Homemade Comics, Issues from: 1960s, 1970s
    - Title from indicia: ProJunior, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Smile, Issues from: 1970s (Box 451)
    - Title from indicia: Snarf, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Super Soul Comix, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Tales from the Fridge, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Teenage Horizons of Shangrila, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: "XYZ" Comics, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Last Gasp/Last Gasp-Eco Funnies
    - Title from indicia: The Adventures of the Little Green Dinosaur, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: American Flyer, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Armageddon, Issues from: [1970s]
    - Title from indicia: Bakersfield Kountry Comics, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Brain Fantasy, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Dopin' Dan, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Dr. Atomic, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Fantagor, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Grim Wit, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Harold Hedd, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Image of the Beast, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Inner City Romance Comic, "Choices", Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Inner City Romance 2: Radical Rock, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: It Ain't Me Babe Comix, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: It Ain't Me Babe: Women's Liberation
    - Title from indicia: Laugh in the Dark, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Legion of Charlies, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Monolith, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Skull, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Slow Death, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Spasm, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Tales from the Leather Nun, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Tortoise and the Hare, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Young Lust, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: The Los Angeles Comic Book Company
    - Title from indicia: Mutants of the Metropolis, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Weird Fantasies, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Myron Moose Comic Book Works
    - Title from indicia: Myron Moose Funnies, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Now and Then Publications
    - Title from indicia: Oktoberfest Comics, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Print Mint
    - Title from indicia: American Flyer Funnies, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Captain, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Captain Guts, Issues from: 1960s, 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Colop, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Despair, Issues from: [1970s] (Box 452)
    - Title from indicia: Deviant Slice Comics, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Feds 'n' Heads, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Heavy Tragicomix, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Insect Fear, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Junkwaffel, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Light Comitragies, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Light
    - Title from indicia: The Man, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Manhunt, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Mean Bitch Thrills, Issues from: [1970s]
    - Title from indicia: Moondog, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Mr. Natural, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: (Not Only) The Best of Wonder Wart-Hog, Volume III, Issues from:1970s
    - Title from indicia: Real Pulp Comics, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: San Francisco Comic Book, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Savage Humor, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Spaced Out, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Tales of Sex and Death, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Truckin', Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Tuff Shit, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Uneeda Comix, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Yellow Dog Comix, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Young Lust, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Zap Comix, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: R. Crumb
    - Title from indicia: Jiz Comics, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: R. Crumb's Comics and Stories, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Snatch Comics, Issues from: 1960s
  - Publisher: Reece, Metzger, Todd, Gasparotti, Tellez
    - Title from indicia: Compost Comics, Issues from: 1970s
  - Publisher: Rip Off Press
    - Title from indicia: Amazon Comics, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Armadillo Comics, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: A Year Passes Like Nothing With The Fabulous Furry Freak Brothers, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Big Ass Comics, Issues from: 1960s, 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Brother, Can You Spare a dime for The Fabulous Furry Freak Brothers?, Issues from:1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Collected Freak Brothers, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Cartoon History of the Universe, Volume 1, The Evolution of Everything, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Cartoon History of the Universe, Volume 2, Sticks and Stones, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Cartoon History of the Universe, Volume 3, River Realms, Issues From: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Cartoon History of the Universe, Volume 4, Part of the Old Testament, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Cartoon History of the Universe, Volume 5, Brains and Bronze, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Cartoon History of the Universe, Volume 6, "Who are These Athenians?", Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Fabulous Furry Freak Brothers, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Fabulous Furry Freak Brothers in "Grass Roots", Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Fabulous Furry Freak Brothers in "The Idiots Abroad", Issues from:1980s